(Leonard:)Thank you. Seriously,
please don't make me go.
(Penny:)Should we take this little
party to the bedroom?
(Leonard:)Don't have to. We have
the whole place to ourselves.
(Penny:)-That's true.
-In fact, if you want,
(Leonard:)we can do it right here
on Sheldon's spot.
(Penny:)That is the least sexy thing
anyone's ever said to me.
-To the bedroom!
-Yeah!
And for the entrée, tonight's
special is a seafood risotto.
(Waiter:)-Do you have any questions?
-I do.
(Sheldon:)Does this train car have
the original link-and-pin coupler
(Sheldon:)or the Miller Hook and platform?
(Waiter:)I'm sorry, I meant
questions about the food.
(Sheldon:)Oh, of course.
(Sheldon:)Is the seafood risotto being
served on a train car
(Sheldon:)with the original
link-and-pin coupler
orthe Miller Hook and platform?
(Amy:)I think we're gonna
need a minute.